Suddenly Explorers! Suddenly explorers!
Hello! Please join us in chatting with everyone at the stand!
I'm Kazukiretameno, under Sakuraba!
Please help me!
I'm Akinari Expedition!
Okay, so today, I'm going to ask these two to explore the Inviniz Rai.
What are we going to do today?
Let's announce the closing of the museum!
This is a popular project! It's so much fun!
It's so much fun!
We've done it twice before.
We haven't done it today, right?
It's our first time!
Since we haven't done it yet, I'm going to ask you to try your hand at closing announcements.
I'm going to ask them to try their hand at announcing the closing of the museum.
Can you do it?
No, I think it's a little difficult.
Well, I don't think I'd have a good voice.
Oh, voices?
Yes, you have a voice.
You have a very distinctive voice, don't you?
You have a unique voice, don't you?
Here she is!
I'm sorry to hear that, but have a nice time!
Why Mr. Rekiin?
Well, it's today.
I'm not too worried about you.
Oh, good!
The problem is that Mr. Hinano went a little too far.
What if he gets a little angry with me?
That's not supposed to happen.
No, I'm an adult now.
Are you okay?
As soon as Mr. Yuna started talking.
E-BiNZ's upper management
They're not going to come running in with their blood on their hands, are they?
That's what scares me the most.
If I say, "Who are you?
That's the biggest trek.
Because it's a trek?
Why do we have to go there?
Well, it's a little original for both of us.
Give it your own personal touch.
We'll be closing soon.
E-BiNZ today.
I have to make an announcement as soon as possible.
Let's go to the information desk and make an announcement.
Let's go to the information desk and do some announcements!
Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
Let's go!
Oh! Let's go!
This way?
Okay, we've arrived at the first floor information desk.
We're here.
Don't clean your eyes.
Don't clean the information lady's eyes.
Your sister's eyes.
I'm not sleeping, I'm working
I'm here to announce the closing of the museum to the two of you now.
Wow, I'm nervous.
The museum will be closing soon.
The whole building, not just the first floor?
It's going to ring throughout the building.
Oh, no.
It's bad, isn't it?
Make sure you announce it.
I'll do my best.
Well, let's have someone inside let us in right away.
Yuna-san first.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Let's just have you show us how to operate this microphone.
Please do.
Yes, sir.
Press the sticker here in the positive direction.
Positive push.
And then...
Yes, okay.
I'm nervous.
Are you okay?
Yes, I am.
Okay, let's start with the first batter.
Yuna-san.
I'll do my best.
What's your enthusiasm?
I'm very nervous.
You're nervous?
I'm more nervous than at a live performance.
I want to win the hearts of the poets before me.
That's a big one.
Then start when you're ready.
Okay, let's do it!
I'm nervous, too.
Here we go.
Okay.
Terere, terere, terere, terere.
Hey Hey Hey
How are you all doing?
It's getting colder these days, are you catching a cold?
In that case, Ramen Opechan!In that case, Ramen Opechan!
Good night.
I love ramen! I love flour!
Soon, I'll be 20 years old!
I'm a member of Nogizaka46...oh! Sorry, I made a mistake!
I'm a member of Momoshiro Kromerset...oh! Sorry, I made a mistake!
I'm Yuna Tsukuki from Ihinari to Ogaku-san!
Hmmm!
To all of you who are enjoying shopping
All of you who are in the middle of a meal.
To all of you who are on summer vacation, summer vacation!
Please let me go up soon! Raise my hourly wage!
To all the employees who are thinking, "I can't wait to get off work!
E-Bee's is about to close!
One more hour, one more hour, one more hour, one more hour, one more hour, one more hour!
One more hour, one more hour, one more hour.
Almost one hour!
Time feels different for everyone.
Time never goes back! It will never come back!
I wish you a better time from 7:00 to 8:00 on September 6, 2022!
So, goodbye!
What did you think?
I don't know.
What if they're chasing us around?
Takano Hina-san!
Who's there?
How was it, Hina-san? Ask him.
Well, um...
It was fun.
The mysterious...
What was it?
I almost laughed and
I was trying to control my feelings.
I was probably in there then too.
I might have picked it up.
I thought it wasn't in there, so I did it.
I liked the hey hey hey.
You're right.
You guys looked like you had it in there together.
It's just...
I'm feeling a little...
Maybe we can take it with us now.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Okay, okay.
It's not the middle of something.
I was just saying.
The one-language character
It just came out on its own.
I'm glad he did.
I'm glad.
Thank you for this valuable experience.
I'll ask your sister at Incomation about it.
I'll ask her how she liked it.
How did you like my announcement?
It was very interesting.
Thank you very much.
It's unique.
Indeed.
It was very good.
Thank you very much.
I would like to continue with Unique Yuna.
I was so nervous.
I mean the end of the top batter
Thank you very much.
Let's go, Hinano-san!
I'll do my best
I'm Yuna.
I'm Yuna, just kidding!
Next, Hinano-san!
Hinano-san's Hiraoi Announcement
Shall we go?
Are you listening in?
I'll try not to laugh.
If you laugh...
I'm serious. I want to joke around.
I have to tell you something.
They say it's time for quiet.
I'll try my best not to laugh
I want to make you stop.
I want to stop you.
Then you can start at your own time.
You can start at your own time.
Good luck!
Laughter
Here we go.
Music
Oh, no, I'm not going to do it... that's a bad idea.
It's easy to descend into a slanting world
You're listening to METAMMER
METAMMER" by Nama Nori Tohoku!
Please listen to the music video on YouTube!
Now! Now!
Yes! Hey there! Open your phone and go to YouTube.
You're probably just walking around on your phone, aren't you?
No! Look where you're going!
Only look ahead! No, just look at me!
Why are you looking ahead? Why? Don't look anywhere but at Hina!
What? Who the hell are you?What? Who the hell are you?
My name is Sakura Hinano.
I'm the one who makes you smile.
Now that I'm here, you'll be all right!
I'm here to make your heart flutter
Why don't you add a little cuteness to your life?
Search and find me, I'm Sakura Hina from Namaori Tohoku!
Hey there! Did you just look at your phone?
Look at the clock!
Soon it will be time to close E-Beans!
Sad! Sad! But this is the reality!
Thank you so much for coming to E-Beans today!
Did you get a lot of shopping done?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! It looks like you did!
I'm glad you had fun!
Well then, have fun and be busy until we close!
After 8pm...
Oh! I shouldn't go there!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Well then, thank you all for coming to E-Beans today!
Come again!
Hohoho!
Hey!
Good night.
Well, that was great.
The start of the show was a publicity stunt.
No way.
Metahammer.
He sang.
His voice was so loud.
I was so surprised.
Oh my God, it was huge.
It's okay, it's okay.
The first song was the first advertisement.
I thought it was Family Mart, not EB.
They are playing that song at FamilyMart.
Sure, I'll give it a try.
How was it singing?
It was fun.
I want to do more.
Want to do more?
Are you interested?
It got me interested.
It's good.
If you want to sing, you should sing live.
That's true.
I don't think there are many people who make this their main venue, singing.
I wanted to see real reactions.
Messages from the audience.
Sure, if we could have two cameras rolling, we could check it out.
I wanted to monitor.
I did!
What? There might have been people doing that.
There might have been.
How was it, Yuna?
Her beautiful voice was all over the place.
I'll probably search for five people.
Five?
That's good.
They were surprised.
From the scene when they started singing.
I thought she was singing.
I thought she was humming.
I thought he was going to stop.
I thought, "Oh, no.
I wasn't sure, but I decided to give it a try.
I'm glad I did.
That's what I'm talking about, Evince.
You really are amazing.
Let's hear what Iromen has to say about this too.
How was it, Hinano-san?
My singing voice is really good.
It was like an impression of the live performance.
It had a huge impact on me.
I think it probably stopped everyone in their tracks.
In a good way.
I'll search for it when I get home.
Yay!
This time I was close.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry for interrupting.
I'm sorry to have disturbed you. Thank you very much.
It was a life experience.
It's true.
I will use it when I'm job hunting.
Will I be able to use it?
No, but...
Announcement type.
That's a bad word then.
You've descended into a slanted world.
I've had the opportunity to experience the information.
I'd like to share my thoughts with you again.
How was it, Hina-san?
I thought you were very free EVINCE.
That's true.
That's for sure.
This is the only place that lets me do this kind of thing.
This is the only place. Even in the whole country.
That's true.
This is the third time.
If we've done it for the third time...
I guess that means there are no NGs.I guess that means NG is not out.
Last time Lung-chan was ringing a lot of phones.
It was ringing, but since it's done this time.
That's for sure. We already have six members.
If we can win them all at this rate.
We only have three more to go.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
How was it, Hina-san?
It was a rare experience for me.
That's for sure.
And the announcements were on average.
It was an intense experience of my life.
It was a very precious experience.
You don't get to do that very often.
If there was a time when there wasn't so much of it, like today in Oita.
Hina-san, you can come here and sing.
Here.
There are a lot of people here.
Can I ask you to prepare an orchestra or something?
Really?
I'm really free to do what I want.
Thank you EVINCE.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to seeing what you can do for us in the future.
Indeed.
I am looking forward to it.
That's all for today's exploration.
If you would like to make an announcement, too, please send it here.
Please send it here.
I can't do it, can I?
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
This is limited to Tohoku-san only.
Please take a look at the next exploration.
Thank you very much.
I'm curious about the expedition.